### Pooja Gangwani

#### Co-Founder at FuerteDevelopers

#### Summary

Pooja is a capable professional who has extensive experience of analyzing current and potential business processes to identify clear opportunities for improvement. With a background in streamlining and automating procedures, she is more than able to not only meet but exceed your expectations in developing best practices.

#### Experience

Co-Founder

January 2017 - Present

# Business Development Manager at Freelance, self-employed January 2017 - Present

- # Establishing contact with all assigned leads by call or e-mail within time frame defined by company.
- # Generate sales leads by outbound calls and e-mail attempts.
- # Understand clients need, Negotiation, Closure.
- # Follow-up to clients/ inquiries.
- # Responsible to generate new clients
- # Identifying deficiencies in business systems.
- # Communication & Interpersonal Skills.
- # Writing up engaging, informative and well-organized presentations.
- # Can manage a flexible work schedule to accommodate different time zones.
- # Business Intelligence.
- # Strategy to understand business or technical issues.
- # Solid collaboration, facilitation, and negotiation skills.
- # Able to work accurately with interruptions.

#### Education

Marwadi College

Master's Degree, Computer Science, 2015 - 2017

Atmiya Institute of Technology & Science (SFI), Rajkot. 787

Bachelor's Degree, Computer Science, 2011 - 2014

## Pooja Gangwani

Co-Founder at FuerteDevelopers



Contact Pooja on LinkedIn